[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States", "United States"]}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", ",", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Are you worried now that they're going to come after you, big brother style, and try and come after your sources?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Well, I mean I think the sources behind this are incredibly courageous people who could have sold this information for extraordinary amounts of money to foreign governments or handed it over, had that been their objective to harm the United States to enemies of the United States.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"], "PERSON": ["Mike Rogers", "Lindsey Graham"]}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "But I mean, what is your reaction to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Well, it's fascinating that the most right-wing members of the Congress like Mike Rogers and Lindsey Graham have become the administration's most vocal defenders.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2008"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "CD", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VB", "NN", "IN", "CC", "IN", "NNPS", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "Was their primary purpose to root out Americans who may be up to no good or foreigners who are up to no good?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "NNPS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Well, under the Surveillance Law that passed in 2008, that the bipartisan Congress passed, they eliminated the warrant requirement for all conversations except ones that take place by and among Americans exclusively on American soil.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "RB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "RBR", "IN", "CD", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "RP", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "You believe them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "I -- there may be some technical basis on which they can say that we are not actively collaborating or that they don't have what we consider in our own definition to be direct access to our servers but what I do know is that I have talked to more than one person who has sat at a desk at a Web portal and typed out commands and reached into those servers from a distance.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "Well, it depends entirely how they're using it and that's the problem with the secrecy here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Senator, this is just unbelievable, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "It is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "That's not freedom, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Not to my mind it's not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush", "Barack Obama", "Bush"]}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NNPS", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Has what Barack Obama has been doing, and his administration, not just with all these revelations in the last 24 hours but also the IRS and going after A.P. and FOX News and so on, when you put it all together, is what he's doing worse than anything George W. Bush did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "I think Bush started the process and what I had hoped and I think millions of Americans had hoped, that Barack Obama, who knew something about constitutional law, would not only change Bush's policies in a number of ways, but certainly with regard to civil liberties.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 24 hours"], "ORGANIZATION": ["IRS", "FOX News"], "PERSON": ["Barack Obama", "George W. Bush"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "How do we know they're not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Well, we know they're not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Do we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Didn't you know that they were targeting Tea Party members through the IRS?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "And we still don't know --", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party", "IRS"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["12 years later"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "Congress", "FBI", "CIA", "FBI"]}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", ",", "TO", "DT", "NNP", ",", "TO", "DT", "NNP", ",", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "RBR", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "CC", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", ",", "WRB", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "But at what point do you draw the line, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "Well, I think, Piers, one of the big problems here has been that our society, the American people, and the Congress, and the media, have basically said to the authorities, to the FBI, to the CIA, and other intelligence services, we will not tolerate one single terrorist death, and that's the problem we've had, is that we had the terrible events of 9/11 and 12 years later, you know, if one or two or four or five people get killed in a terrorist attack, people are outraged, the FBI dropped the ball, why didn't they know about this, how come they can't read the bad guys' minds.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "So it's kind of a symptom, really, of modern times, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Well, that's absolutely true, that you would not have had this capability.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "Did you know your son was going to do this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "I actually -- I did know that he was going to do it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Would the audience have been as supportive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Well, I would have absolutely been as supportive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", ":", "NN", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "But how do you think it would have played out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "I don't think he would -- something like that would have had that kind of a reaction.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "How important is it for people like your son maybe to stand up on behalf of the young and say what he did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "I think it's incredibly important.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Dershowitz"]}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "You agree?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Well, I think Mr. Dershowitz got it right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 395, "question": "Where do you draw the line?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 396, "answer": "That's the question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "ORGAN: Where would you draw the line?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Well, I don't know exactly what they've done here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "I live in New York, if you become mayor, are you going to start snooping on my e-mails?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "Look, the city of New York, I don't believe, has that power or will ever have that power.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Would you like it to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 427, "question": "I mean, you're still ahead of him but he's creeping up, isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "You know, look --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["New Yorkers"]}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Is it appropriate for New Yorkers to vote as their mayor somebody who sent naked pictures of himself over the Internet to random women?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "WP", "NN", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Look, that's for New Yorkers to decide.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Yorkers"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Yorkers"]}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "What do you think as a New Yorker?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "I know New Yorkers are going to vote for the candidate, me, who has the longest record of delivering for them because what they care about is that -- they've gotten and are going to get more housing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "How did you come through it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "Well, you know, it's very tough when you lose a parent when you're young and she was sick for about 10 years so most of my time with her, she was sick and it's hard because you feel as a child that somehow you're responsible, even though you know you're not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "I don't -- I mean, everybody in the world has issues with food, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "You look fantastic to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "Do you ever recover fully from bulimia?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "You know, I'm not bulimic now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 508, "question": "You support -- what's happened here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "Look, the case --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Texas"]}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Yes or no?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Under Texas law, this is perfectly legal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", ":", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "You support it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "And a jury -- and a jury acquitted the guy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 538, "question": "You shoot a woman dead because she may or may not have taken $150?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "CC", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "$", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "I can't say --", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$150"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Texas"]}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "And a jury, and a courtroom in America, allows you to just walk out and go home to do it again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Look, I can't say I agree with the Texas law, either.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Texas"]}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "Do you not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "No, I don't agree with the Texas law.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130606pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "This story I had earlier about this high school valedictorian speech, are you in favor of it, Margaret?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Margaret"]}}]